# Gaston Artigas

Integration Specialist

&

Frontend Developer

**About me** 

Technical skills

Soft skills

# **Gaston Ezequiel Artigas Ciabattini**

Morón, Buenos Aires Argentina

+5491152630925

gastonartcia@gmail.com

PortFolio (gartcia-portfolio.netlify.app)

I'm currently a student of Computer Science at UBA and I'm working on Fudo, a gastronomic software.

I'm a Frontend Developer who works on his own projects in his free time. I'm always studying new technologies to develop new projects.

- Experience in CRM (Hubspot and Zendesk).
- Office experience.
- Training experience.
- Experience in leadership.
- Current stack:

HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, JQuery, Redux, Bootstrap, Tailwind, SASS.

- Excellent communication skills, both oral and written.
- Excellent comprehension skills.
- Strong interest in technology in general.
- Always looking for improvements in the area in which you work.
- Interest in personal and professional growth.

# **Experience**

# Fudo, Integration Specialist

September 2022 - Present

- Integration process management
- Ticket tracking in Hubspot
- Training in related areas
- Representative for contacts with delivery apps
- Contact with integration requesters
- Internal area training
- Presentation of process improvements in the area
- Weekly performance reports

#### Fudo, Customer Support

April 2021 - September 2022

- Troubleshooting
- Installation of command and fiscal printers (USB, serial and ethernet)
- Ticket tracking in Hubspot and Zendesk
- Referral of cases from outside the area
- Weekly performance reports

# **Formation**

# **Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science**

2020 - Presente

Facultad de Ciencias Exactas, UBA

# **Commercial Bachelor**

2013-2019

Escuela Superior de Comercio Carlos Pellegrini